http://www.regal-diving.co.uk/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Our friendly and experienced team are ready to take your call today. We look forward to hearing from you!
Call Regaldive:
Monday to Friday, 9am to 6pm
all year except UK public holidays
9am to 1pm on Saturday during January, February & March
Tel: 01353 659999
Write to Regaldive:
Email: info@regaldive.co.uk
Outside normal working hours, or in the unlikely event we are unable to take your call, please leave amessage on our answerphone and we will call you back as soon as possible.
For guests travelling with Regaldive requiring urgent assistance, please refer to your travel notes forrelevant contact information.
×
Send Enquiry
CALL01353 659999
Business Hours
Contact Us
Our friendly and experienced team are ready to take your call today. We look forward to hearing from you!
Call Regaldive:
Monday to Friday, 9am to 6pm
all year except UK public holidays
9am to 1pm on Saturday during January, February & March
Tel: 01353 659999
Write to Regaldive:
Regaldive
Long Barn South
Sutton Manor Farm
Bishop's Sutton
Alresford
Hampshire
SO24 0AA
Email: info@regaldive.co.uk
Outside normal working hours, or in the unlikely event we are unable to take your call, please leave amessage on our answerphone and we will call you back as soon as possible.
For guests travelling with Regaldive requiring urgent assistance, please refer to your travel notes forrelevant contact information.
×
Send Enquiry
More
More
Why choose Regaldive
Loyalty discounts
Insurance
Airport Parking & Hotels
Liveaboard Trips
On-board accommodation offering the opportunity to live right over the dive sites and to experience secluded dives...
Diving regions...
LATEST AVAILABILITY BY REGION
Red Sea availability
Maldives availability
Indonesian availability
Socorro Mexico availability
Galapagos availability
ALL LIVEABOARD DIVING REGIONS
Bahamas
Diving Destinations
Discover some of the world’s finest dive destinations with Regaldive...
DIVING REGIONS...
RED SEA (EGYPT)
All Red Sea
Sharm el Sheikh
Hurghada
El Gouna
Soma Bay
Safaga
El Quseir
Marsa Alam
Curacao
Egypt (Red Sea)
Galapagos
Grenada and Carriacou
Indonesia
Lanzarote, Canaries
Maldives
Malta and Gozo
Mexico
Oman
Truk Lagoon
Our Top destinations....
Red Sea (Egypt)
Maldives
Indonesia
Mexico
Galapagos
Philippines
Sudan
Why not try....
Liveaboard Diving
Short Break Diving Holidays
Philippines Island Hopping
Home
Destinations
Liveaboards
Dive Courses
OffersLiveaboard Offers
Liveaboard
Where would you like to go?
AllEgypt (Red Sea)CaribbeanIndonesiaPhilippinesMaldivesAzoresThailandMalta and GozoMexicoOmanBahamasLanzarote (Canaries)South AfricaTanzaniaBorneo (Malaysia)
AllManado, North SulawesiMarsa AlamBali DivingGrenada and CarriacouHurghadaPhuketSharm El SheikhIsland HoppingLuxor ExtensionsRiviera MayaSao MiguelTobagoBonaireDumaguete and DauinEl GounaGozo DivingMalta DivingMuscatNassauPuerto Del CarmenSafagaBoholCozumelEl QuseirHamataMakadi BayPicoSoma Bay and Abu SomaAngaga IslandAnilaoBangkokBoutique Beach - Dhigurah IslandCoron (Palawan)CuraçaoDerawan, East KalimantanEllaidhoo IslandEriyadu IslandFilitheyo IslandFlores and KomodoKrabi's Ao NangLayang LayangMafia IslandMalapascuaMaluku Islands (Moluccas)Maradhoo IslandMedhufushi IslandMeeru Island ResortMindoroPemba IslandReethi Beach Island
Beach Fronted
Dive Centre on Site
Nitrox Available
House Reef
Diving Included
Double Cabins
Open Advanced Search +
Diving Ability Level
Beginner (Want to learn)
4-10 Logged Dives
11-30 Logged Dives
31-50 Logged dives
51+ Logged Dives
Mixed Experience
Holiday Budget Per Person
Up to £600
Up to £1200
129Matching trips
Where would you like to go?
AllEgypt (Red Sea)MaldivesMexicoIndonesiaGalapagos, EcuadorCocos Island (Costa Rica)PalauThailandTruk Lagoon (Micronesia)BahamasOmanPhilippinesCaribbean
Nitrox Available
Double Cabins
Diving Included
When would you like to go?
AllDecember 2020January 2021February 2021March 2021April 2021May 2021June 2021July 2021August 2021September 2021October 2021November 2021December 2021January 2022February 2022March 2022April 2022May 2022June 2022July 2022August 2022September 2022October 2022November 2022December 2022January 2023February 2023March 2023April 2023May 2023June 2023July 2023August 2023September 2023October 2023November 2023December 2023January 2024February 2024March 2024April 2024May 2024June 2024July 2024August 2024September 2024October 2024November 2024December 2024
Open Advanced Search +
Diving Ability Level
11-30 Logged Dives
31-50 Logged dives
51+ Logged Dives
Mixed Experience
Holiday Budget Per Person
Up to £600
67Matching trips
Privacy PolicyRegaldive Privacy CentreWhile the policy statement below covers the finer details, we can sum it up as follows. We respect and protect your privacy and follow stringent procedures for using and storing your personal data. We never sell or share your personal information, or let other organisations use it for marketing purposes. We don’t abuse the trust you place in us when you send us an enquiry.overviewThis policy statement explains how we collect information from you and how we use it when you contact us about our services. This statement forms part of our website Terms and Conditions.Regadive is part of The Natural Travel Collection Ltd. You can contact us here.The Natural Travel Collection LtdLong Barn South,Sutton Manor FarmBishop’s SuttonAlresfordHampshireSO24 0AAUnited KingdomCompany Registration Number 7860375 We are members of the ICO Data Protection Register (ZA271212). You can find out further information by visiting the ICO website. HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATIONWe collect personal information about you when you make an enquiry for our products and services. We also collect information when you provide holiday feedback, participate in competitions and attend events.We also collect details about the pages you visit on our website. Please see our cookies policy below for more information.how we use your personal dataCommunications and MarketingWe request personal information such as your name and email address when you subscribe to our newsletters or send us a message from our Enquiry Form. We need to collect this information for personalisation and it is used to help us provide you with the service that you have requested. The information we collect, if you agree, will be used for marketing purposes about our holidays and services that we think may be of interest to you. Depending on your selected preferences we will send details of our latest holidays, special offers, events and inspirational travel news by email and/or travel brochures by post. You have the opportunity to opt out of all marketing material and communications received.We collect aggregate information about our web visitors such as quantity of visits to each webpage and browser type. This data may be used to customise Regaldive web content to deliver a better experience for our users and will in no way personally identify you.Agreeing to our privacy policy allows us to use your information to offer you all of our products and services at The Natural Travel Collection.ProcessingWe collect information about you in order to process your holiday enquiry and fulfil your booking request. This will require us to pass relevant information on to the suppliers of your travel arrangements such as airlines, hotels and transport companies.Third PartiesBe assured that we will not share or sell your personal information to third parties without your consent. However, we reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Regaldive’s rights or property, other users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.SECURITYProtecting the security of all personally-identifiable information associated with our clients is of the utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information. Once we receive your details, we will take all reasonable precautions to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our users’ personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose to us online.LINKS TO OTHER SITESYou should be aware that when you are on our website, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from out website pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may significantly differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.cookiesWhat are cookies?A cookie is a small piece of data sent from websites you visit and, if you agree, is stored in your web browser. The cookie assists in analysing visitors to our website to ensure we give you the best experience. No information that identifies you personally is collected.What cookies do we use?We use different types of cookies, some of which are essential for our website to work. We use both ‘first-party cookies’ and ‘third-party cookies’.First-party cookies are set by us and we use them and the data that they gather for our own purposes which allow us to analyse the use of our website.Third-party cookies are set by other websites that are connected to our website, for example a social network whose share buttons we display (such as Facebook and Twitter). These third parties can recognise your computer or device when you visit both on our website and elsewhere on the internet.These cookies are anonymous and do not gather information that can personally identify you.How can I manage cookies?You can manage cookies through your browser settings at anytime and decline cookies if you prefer.Internet Explorer: Select Tools in the top navigation bar in your browser, and go to Options then Privacy to adjust the cookie settings.Google Chrome: Select Tools in the top navigation bar in your browser, and select Options then the Under the Hood tab, Privacy then Content settings.Mozilla Firefox: Select Tools in the top navigation bar in your browser, and go to Options, then select Privacy and click on Cookies.Safari: Select the cog icon in the top navigation bar in your browser and select Preferences, then Security to access cookie options.To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.orgACCESS TO YOUR OWN DATA & OPTING OUTYou have the right to be provided with a copy of your own personal data, to contest and correct inaccuracies, request personal data to be deleted, or opt-out of receiving marketing communications. Contact us. Any data queries will be actioned promptly upon receipt.your acceptance of these termsBy using this site, you signify your acceptance to this Regaldive Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.If you need help or have any questions about this policy and your rights with regards to the processing of your personal information please contact us. 5 November 2018
Next Steps
Inspire Me
EMAIL US
CALL 01353 659999
Dive in with us!
Sign up to the Regaldive newsletter and be the first to know about
the latest offers and news from the underwater world
Email:
First name:
Last name:
Subscribe
JOIN US ON FACEBOOK!
Regaldive Worldwide
FOLLOW US ON TWITTER
Tweets by @Regaldive
FROM THE BLOG
New Small Group Dive Adventures for 2021!
Is it time to get your liveaboard fix from land? Based at a carefully selected resort you can enjoy...
Diving News
We are very excited the Maldives and Lanzarote have recently joined Grenada as dive destinations...
Emperor Fleet Autumn Sale 2020
Grab a great deal during October 2020 with our good friends at Emperor Divers!
